Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore
  - Subseries C: Festivals and Conferences
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, MJ BBC" Correspondence and Licence Agreement (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Calender" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance 98," Badge, Pass, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Mary Jane: "Festivals, Ferndale" Invoice and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Mary Jane: "Scotland Ten Day Weekend," Correspondence and Information Pack, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Mary Jane: "South Carolina Carolina" South Carolina Arts Commission Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Mary Jane: "CMJ Film Fest '99" Badge and Pass, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Mary Jane: "LadyFest East 2002" Schedule (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Mary Jane: USA Festival Badges and Passes, undated (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Tour" Badges and Passes, undated (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Subseries D: Press and Film Reviews
    Subseries D: Press and Film Reviews, includes press releases, film reviews and flyers for the feature film.
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press 1996" (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press 1996" (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Mary Jane: Spin, Nov 1997 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Mary Jane: "MPLS Press 2/19/1997" (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press 1998" (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press Jan-May", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press 1998" (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Original Press, Special Projects" (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Mary Jane: Original Press 1999" (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Mary Jane: "Original Press 1999" (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Mary Jane: "MJ Press 2001" (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Subseries E: Media Originals
    Conditions Governing Access
    Subseries E: Media Originals, includes production elements for the feature film.
    - Mary Jane: Reel 1 of 2, 16mm Access Film Print, 1996; ID: 157.0003 (Reel 157.0003)
    - Mary Jane: Reel 2 of 2, 16mm Access Film Print, 1996; ID: 157.0004 (Reel 157.0004)
    - Mary Jane: 16mm Film and Magnetic Track Production Elements, 1996; ID: 157.0006 - .0089 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0006 - .0089)
    - Mary Jane: 1/4" Reel-to-Reel Audio Production Elements, 1996; ID: 157.0090 - .0110 (Box 17, Media ID: 157.0090 - .0110)
    - Mary Jane: "Mary Jane Tryouts", undated; ID: 157.0225 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0225)
    - Mary Jane: "Mary Jane's Not Anymore (Excerpt) RT 13:38, A Film by Sarah Jacobson 646/486-1094", 1996; ID: 157.0226 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0226)
      TRT: 00:13:38
    - Mary Jane: "CNBC Sundance 97, 1-20-97", 1997; ID: 157.0228 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0228)
    - Mary Jane: "13 Feb 97 Channel 9 News, Jacobson -- Review, Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore", 1997; ID: 157.0229 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0229)
    - Mary Jane: "Austin Ch 2", undated; ID: 157.0230 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0230)
    - Mary Jane: Negative Trims, 16mm (Reel 157.0089)
  - Subseries F: 2018 Accretion
    Subseries F: 2018 Accretion production materials from her independent film project Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore.
    - Mary Jane auditions, Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Mary Jane shirt, Undated (Box 40)
- Series III: The Stains Documentary
  Series III contains materials related to the production and research of Jacobson's documentary on the making of motion picture film, Ladies and Gentlemen, The Fabulous Stains.
  - Subseries A: Production Materials and Research
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Debbie Rashon" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Diane Lane" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Nancy [Dowd]" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Fee Waybill" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Stains: "Statins Log: Jake" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Christine Laiti" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Steve Jones" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Stains: "Stains Log: Lou Alder" Interview, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Stains: All Washed Up, Origial Script by Nancy Dowd, 2nd Draft, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Stains: All Washed Up, Original Script by Nancy Dowd, 4th Draft, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Stains: "Special Circumstances" Original Script by Nancy Dowd, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Subseries B: Media Originals
    - Stains: "Fee Waybill Interview", 1999; ID: 157.0119 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0119)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      DVD access copy available.
      Duration: 38 minutes
- Series IV: Professional Projects
  Series IV contains materials related to some of Jacobson's professional projects and jobs, completed and in progress. Includes such items as clippings, related media, artifacts, flyers, and research.
  - Subseries A: Stationwagon Productions
    Subseries A: Stationwagon Productions, includes materials related to Jacobson's work for Stationwagon Productions.
    - Station Wagon: "Rejection Letters", 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Station Wagon: "Film Shows by Sarah Jacobson", 1995 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Station Wagon: "Conversations with Allison Anders, Tamra Davis, Sarah Jacobson", 1995 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Station Wagon: "Distribution Jack Stevenson", 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Subseries B: Sleaze
    Subseries B: Sleaze includes materials related to the development of Jacobson's work-in-progress script, Sleaze.
    - Sleaze: IFM Market Pass, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 179)
      See Related Media, Series J.
  - Subseries C: The Adventures of Sweet Miss: The Disco Years
    Subseries C: The Adventures of Sweet Miss: The Disco Years includes items related to Jacobson's film, The Adventures of Sweet Miss.
    - Sweet Miss: Ediburgh Film Festival Calender, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Sweet Miss: "LadyFest Midwest" Festival, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Subseries D: Hardcorn (see Oversize for related material)
    Subseries D: Hardcorn includes material related to the production of Jacobson's comic, Hardcorn.
    - Hardcorn: "Comic Book Materials", 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Hardcorn: "Original Flyers", 19937 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Hardcorn: Hardcorn #1, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Hardcorn: Hardcorn #2, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Subseries E: Film Festivals and Conferences
    Subseries E: Film Festivals and Concerts includes calendars, passes, and flyers of various national and international film festivals.
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival Calender, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival Calender, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Film Festivals: New York Underground Film Festival Calender, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Film Festivals: "Tubes Badge", 1997 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival Calender, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival, Badge/Pass, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival Calender, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival, Badge/Pass, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival, Badge/Pass, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Film Festivals: Independent Directors Bruch, Badge/Pass, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Film Festivals: New York Underground Film Festival Calender, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Film Festivals: Sound Unseen Calender, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Film Festivals: New York Underground Film Festival Calender, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Film Festivals: New York Underground Film Festival, Badge/Pass, undated (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Film Festivals: Investor Discovery, Badge/Pass, undated (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Film Festivals: Chicago Underground Film Festival, Badge/Pass, undated (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Film Festivals: Independent Film Channel, Badge/Pass, undated (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Film Festivals: Untitled Badge/Pass, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Subseries F: VH1
    Subseries F: VH1 includes materials related to Jacobson's work for VH1.
    - VH1: Behind the Music, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - VH1: Radical Cheerleaders, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Subseries G: Oxygen Media
    Subseries G: Oxygen Media, includes materials related to Jacobson's work for Oxygen Media.
    - Oxyen: Ladyfest Segment, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Oxygen: ABC No Rio Segment, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Film '99", 2000 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 1 of 22:DV1 Phucky Bitches, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 2 of 22:DV2 Phucky Bitches, POS #2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 3 of 22:DV3 Tanya Monique, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 4 of 22:DV4 Tanya Monique #2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 5 of 22:DV5 Interns Speak, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 6 of 22:DV6 Intern-O-Rama Simone and Sharon, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 7 of 22:DV8-311 Inteview B-Roll, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 8 of 22:DVI9-311 Interviews, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 9 of 22:DVI0 No Doubt Interview/B-Roll, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 10 of 22:DV11 Beta 1 Michael Lange, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 11 of 22: Beta 2 Michael Lange, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 13 of 22:Beta 4 Luna Chicks, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 14 of 22:Beta 5 Luna Chicks, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 15 of 22:Beta 6 Emily, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 16 of 22:Beta 7 Emily, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 17 of 22:Beta 8 Brian Security, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 18 of 22:Beta 9 No Doubt, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 19 of 22:DV10 No Doubt, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 20 of 22:Concert Pos, Washington Square Park #1, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 21 of 22:Concert Pos, Washington Square Park #2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Folder 22 of 22:B-Roll Warped Footage, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Oxygen: "Woodstock Concert Safety Logs," Original Binder, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Oxygen: "Trackers - Audra ISW", 2000 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Oxygen: "Graffiti Tats Crew" Segment, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Subseries H: 50/50
    Subseries H: 50/50 includes Jacobson's work for 50/50.
    - 50/50: "Relevent Articles for 50/50", 1981-1995 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - 50/50: "Women Directors", 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - 50/50: "Esther Bell Godass, Skidmarks", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - 50/50: "Our First Time Show, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - 50/50: "Sticker Action", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - 50/50: "Women Filmmakers Summit", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - 50/50: "Sticker Stats", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - 50/50: "Alice Locas", 2002 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - 50/50: "Reel Women, Alice Guy Blache, Czarina of the Silent Screen", undated (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - Subseries I: Writing Files
    Subseries I: Writing Files includes materials related to Jacobson's freelance writing.
    - Writing: "Filth Articles", 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Writing: "Early Writing/Articles", 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Writing: "New Sassy Sucks", 1994 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Writing: "Caroline Coon", 1994 (Box 4, Folder 247)
      See Related Media, Subseries J.
    - Writing: "Cauleen Smith", 1995 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Writing: "A Conversation with Allison Anders", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Writing: "Penelope Spheeris", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 250)
      See Related Media Subseries J.
    - Writing: "Articles Original '97", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Writing: "George [Kuchar] Artice", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Writing: "George Kuchar -- Some Left Coast Culture Magazine", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Writing: "Punk Planet Rec'd Letters", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Writing: "Punk Planet Articles", 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Writing: "Katrina de Mar, Gang Girls 2000, IFC Rant", 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Writing: "Todd Verow, Shucking the Curve", 1998 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Writing: "Kurt and Courtney", 1998 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Writing: Metallica Article, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Writing: Playboy Mini-Adult", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Writing: "Metallica Drummer", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Writing: Run Lola Run, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 262)
      See Related Media, Suberies J.
    - Writing: "Craig Baldwin", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Writing: "Craig Baldwin, Spectres of the Spectrum", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Writing: "Writer's Contracts", 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Writing: "Publicist List", 2001 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Writing: "Rant Rock Films", 2001 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Writing: "Articles Mounted," YM, May 2002 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Writing: "YM Nikki Reed", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Writing: "Allison Anders, Behind the Sun", undated (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Writing: Bandits Katja Von Garnier, undated (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Writing: "Cool Teens", undated (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Writing: "Nick Broomfield," Axcess Magazine, undated (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Writing: "Venus Manifesto," Ladyfest, undated (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Writing: "White Apache", undated (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Subseries J: Media Originals
    Scope and Contents Note
    Subseries J: Media Originals includes any media items related to the above subseries. Items include audio recordings of interviews conducted for freelance writing, VHI, and the development of Sleaze.
    - Sleaze: "Maureen Interview, Sleaze", undated; ID: 157.0121 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0121)
      Duration: 63 minutes
    - Sleaze: "Ian Mackaye, Sleaze", undated; ID: 157.0123 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0123)
      Duration: 75 minutes
    - VH1: "Radical Cheerleaders, Mary X-mess", undated; ID: 157.0125 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0125)
      Duration: 62 minutes
    - VH1: "A) Radical Cheerleaders #2 B) Aimee and Cara", undated; ID: 157.0127 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0127)
      Duration: 43 minutes
    - VH1: "A) Samantha Radical Cheerleeders 4/23/01 B) Mary X-mess Spin 12/04/01 Pt 1", 2001; ID: 157.0129 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0129)
      Duration: 56 minutes
    - VH1: "George Moll, Behind the Music", undated; ID: 157.0131 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0131)
      Duration: 29 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - VH1: "Gay Rosenthal, Behind the Music", 1999; ID: 157.0133 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0133)
      Duration: 52 minutes
    - Oxygen Media: "Audra Tour Stories", 1999; ID: 157.0135 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0135)
      Duration: 38 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - Oxygen Media: "Audra, ISW", 1999; ID: 157.0137 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0137)
    - Writing File: "Kurt and Courtney", undated; ID: 157.0139 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0139)
      Duration: 46 minutes
    - Writing File: "A) Nick Broomfield B) Cube", undated; ID: 157.0141 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0141)
      Duration: 67 minutes
    - Writing File: "Caroline Coon Tape 1 8/98", 1998; ID: 157.0143 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0143)
    - Writing File: "Caroline Coon Tape 2 8/98", 1998; ID: 157.0145 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0145)
      Duration: 23 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - Writing File: "George Kuchar", undated; ID: 157.0147 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0147)
      Duration: 59 minutes
      Contains significant discussion and criticism of Flaherty Film Seminar
    - Writing File: "Tori Interview 2/27/02," YM Magazine, 2002; ID: 157.0149 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0149)
      Duration: 27 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #1", undated; ID: 157.0151 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0151)
      Duration: 64 minutes; Preservation note: Significant electronic buzzing throughout the interview
    - Writing File: "Allison Anders, Things Behind the Sun #2", 1992-1994; ID: 157.0153 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0153)
      Duration: 41 minutes; Preservation note: Significant electronic buzzing throughout interview
    - Writing File: Run Lola Run, undated; ID: 157.0155 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0155)
      Duration: 48 minutes
    - Writing File: "Penelope Spheeris Sept. 1998", ID: 157.0157 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0157)
      Duration: 65 minutes
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 1", undated; ID: 157.0159 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0159)
      Duration: 64 minutes
    - Writing File: "Christina Kelly, Sassy Pt 2", undated; ID: 157.0161 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0161)
      Duration: 35 minutes
    - Writing File: "A) Mary X-mess Spin 12/04/01, Pt 2 B) Steve Duncombe", 2001; ID: 157.0163 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0163)
      Duration: 47 minutes; Preservation note: significant electronic buzzing on side 2.
    - Writing File: "Mark Mothersbaugh!!", 1992-1994; ID: 157.0165 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0165)
    - Writing File: "Tamra YM Interview", undated; ID: 157.0167 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0167)
      Duration: 25 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - Writing File: "A) Don Letts B) Katja von Gernier Pt 1", undated; ID: 157.0169 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0169)
    - Writing File: "Katja Von Gernier Pt 2", undated; ID: 157.0171 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0171)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Duration: 11 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - Writing File: "A) Cool Teen Favita 6/26/02 B) Nikki Reed 6/29/02", 2002; ID: 157.0173 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0173)
    - Writing File: "Rosewood Follow Up Questions 2/28 and 3/1" YM Article, 2002; ID: 157.0175 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0175)
      Duration: 35 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - "Fluffy," 16mm reversal film (image only), undated; ID: 157.0117 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0117)
      Format: Audio Cassette, Donated Element
      TRT: A) 00:30:00 B) 00:30:00
    - Spferic Waves: "Alexander Yeung, Man or Astroman? Spferic Waves 03/19/95", undated; ID: 157.0231 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0231)
- Series V: Miscellaneous Media Originals
  Series V contains unidentified and miscellaneous media items including audio recordings, video recordings, and 16mm film. Some items may be related to Professional Projects in Series IV and Other Authors in Series VI. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings
    Subseries A contains donated elements, unidentified and miscellaneous audio cassettes.
    - "Lori and Dale," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0179 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0179)
      CD access copy available.
    - "Dale and Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0181 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0181)
    - "Babes: Lori," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0183 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0183)
      Duration: 94 minutes
    - "Babes: Dana, Kat," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0185 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0185)
    - "Babes: Dana," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0187 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0187)
    - "Steve Albini", August 24, 1998; ID: 157.0189 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0189)
      Duration: 58 minutes
    - "A) Radical Cheerleaders #1 B) Aimee and Cara", undated; ID: 157.0191 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0191)
    - "Allison Anders 6/99", 1999; ID: 157.0193 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0193)
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 1", undated; ID: 157.0195 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0195)
    - "Becky Johnson Tape 2", 1992; ID: 157.0197 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0197)
    - "Carine Alder Interview", undated; ID: 157.0199 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0199)
      Duration: 28 minutes; Side 2 is blank
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #1", undated; ID: 157.0201 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0201)
    - "Carla Rockergrrl #2", undated; ID: 157.0203 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0203)
      Duration: 60 minutes
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 1", undated; ID: 157.0205 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0205)
    - "Debbie Gordon Tape 2", undated; ID: 157.0207 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0207)
    - "Jennie L", undated; ID: 157.0209 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0209)
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 1", undated; ID: 157.0211 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0211)
      Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: Tape was incubated due to hydrolysis.
    - "Joe O' Neill Tape 2", undated; ID: 157.0213 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0213)
      Duration: 68 minutes
    - "A) Silkworm, Tim B) Silkworm, Tim, Andy", undated; ID: 157.0215 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0215)
      Duration: 91 minutes
    - "A) Bis B) Todd Verow", 1992; ID: 157.0217 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0217)
      Duration: 55 minutes
    - "Tamra's Interview", undated; ID: 157.0219 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0219)
      Duration: 41 minutes
    - "Lori 2/15/1997," Babes in Toyland, undated; ID: 157.0221 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0221)
      Format: Microcassette; Duration: 61 minutes; Preservation note: Muted audio, electronic hum heard throughout
    - "Susan #1", undated; ID: 157.0222 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0222)
      Currently available.
      Format: Microcassette; Duration: 21 minutes; Preservation note: Side 1 is blank, electronic hum heard throughout
    - Continuation of Lori, 2/15/97, 1997; ID: 157.0223 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0223)
      Format: Microcassette; Duration: 62 minutes; Preservation note: Muted audio, electronic hum heard throughout
    - Unidentified 1/4" Reel-to-Reel Audio, undated; ID: 157.0111- .0112 (Box 17, Media ID: 157.0111- .0112)
    - "Gashuffer," 1/4" Audiocassette, undated; ID: 157.0113 (Box 17, Media ID: 157.0113)
    - "Messiah Scene," 1/4" Reel-to-Reel Audio, undated; ID: 157.0118A (Box 17, Media ID: 157.0118A)
    - "Messiah Scene," Paper Element, undated; ID: 157.0118B (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0118B)
      See Box 4, Folder 275A.
    - "Babes: Lori Barbero" Babes in Toyland, February 1997; ID: 157.0177 (Box 16, Audiocassette ID: 157.0177)
  - Subseries B: Television Appearances Featuring Sarah Jacobson
    Subseries B contains miscellaneous donated elements, video recordings that feature Sarah Jacobson in television programming as a participant.
    - "KRON CH 4, 2-22-97, 3 Min Feature in Office", 1994; cuid41436 (Box 33, Vhs ID: 157.0234)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 23 minutes
    - "Sarah Jacobson -- K-EYE TV Austin, 42 Wedding", February 2, 1998; cuid41437 (Box 33, Vhs ID: 157.0235)
      Duration: 6 minutes
    - "Potpourri A Video Forum #254-KTSF 163, 28:50, Featuring Sarah Jacobson", June 5, 1998; cuid41438 (Box 33, Vhs ID: 157.0236)
      Duration: 30 minutes
    - "Sarah Bay TV", June 1998; cuid41439 (Box 33, Vhs ID: 157.0237)
      Duration: 17 minutes; Preservation note: Though this recording is two hours long, only the Sarah Jacobson's 17 minute appearance was digitized.
    - "Me On Split Screen -- IFFCON", 1998; cuid41440 (Box 33, Vhs ID: 157.0238)